<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on #ReachAAUt</title>
    <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on #ReachAAUt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 12:37:23 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Petar Popovski</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/podcast/petar-popovski/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/podcast/petar-popovski/</guid>
      <description>Petar Popovski uses Blogs on Medium and Linkedin to shape the discussion about 5G.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcasting</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/resources/podcasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/resources/podcasting/</guid>
      <description>Long form audio has been gaining popularity in the past few years and is an excellent format to communicate complex content efficiently. Learn how podcasts can be used for research dessminiation and how you can start an own podcast series without investing much time or resources.
By using the app Anchor, it becomes simple to create your first podcast. You will only need a phone to record it and you can edit the podcast on your phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming - Webpage building</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/upcoming-webpage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/upcoming-webpage/</guid>
      <description>For individuals, research projects or groups, using only open source software and services.
Key facts Dates
 17.03.2021, 2 - 3.30pm 23.03.2021, 2 - 3.30pm 29.03.2021, 2 - 3.30pm  Time: 1.5h
Place: Zoom
Lecturer Daniel is an Associate Professor in Data Science &amp;amp; Innovation Economics at the Aalborg University Business School, where he leads the Data Science research track at the AI:Growth lab. His research is dedicated to the development and application of data-driven methods to map, understand, and predict technological change, and its causes and consequences for socioeconomic systems on various levels of aggregation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/resources/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/resources/blog/</guid>
      <description>Writing an academic blog post is a great way to disseminate your research and expand your network even more. A blog enables you to access new audiences outside your close peer-community – for instance businesses and policy makers. Like other digital academic engagement, publishing a blog will not necessarily translate into more citations for your publications but it may increase attention on your work among practitioners and may even land you invites to give keynotes or to act as a consultant outside academia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacob Brix</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/podcast/jacob_brix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/podcast/jacob_brix/</guid>
      <description>Jacob Brix uses LinkedIn and Twitter to promote his research and shape discussion around organisational learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olga Gurova</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/podcast/olga-gurova/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/podcast/olga-gurova/</guid>
      <description>Olga Gurova explains how she uses her webpage as her business card</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discussion - Research Dissemination</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/wbn-discu1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/wbn-discu1/</guid>
      <description>In this video Antonia Scholkmann, Mathieu Jacomy and Roman Jurowetzki discuss and share their thoughts about research dissemination.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discussion - Research Dissemination</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/wbn-discu2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/wbn-discu2/</guid>
      <description>In this video Michael S Dahl, Massimo Pizzol and Daniele Dell´Aglioi discuss the topic research dissemination where they will share their thoughts and experiences.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Blog for Research Dissemination</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/webinar-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/webinar-blog/</guid>
      <description>Mathieu Jacomy is the creator of Gephi (but not lead developer) and currently PhD Fellow at TANTLAB. In this video he will share his experience with blogging and the creation of one of the most popular network analysis packages. Here he will present his blog.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use podcast for Research Dissemination</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/webinar-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/webinar-podcast/</guid>
      <description>In this video the associate professor at the Business School Roman Jurowetzki talks about how to use podcast for your research dissemination. He tells about how he has turned a Corona teaching project into a real podcast on innovation studies called InnoTalks.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Social Medias for Research Dissemination</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/webinar-some/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/webinar-some/</guid>
      <description>In this video Massimo Pizzol presents how you can use social medias for research dissemination. Massimo is associate proffesor at the Department of Planning at Aalborg University. In this video he shares his experience with using LinkedIn and Twitter for communicating his research. He will also show how you easily can start blogging about your research. In the end of the video he gives you his does and don&amp;rsquo;ts about using social media for research dissemination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Twitter for Research Dissemination</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/webinar-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/webinar-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Antonia Scholkmann is associate professor at the department of culture and learning at Aalborg University. In this video she shares her experience about her experience with Twitter where she engages and connects with her community and other stakeholders.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Websites for Research Dissemination</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/webinar-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/webinar-website/</guid>
      <description>In this video you be presented for Michael S Dahl who is professor in Strategy and Organisation at Aalborg University. He will share his experience with Github-pages as an elegant solution for academic webpages as well as his outreach on Twitter. He will present his webpage.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Websites for Research Dissemination</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/webinar-website2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/events/webinar-website2/</guid>
      <description>Daniele Dell´Aglioi tells in this video about his experiences with using websites for research dissemination. He is an assistant professor in the Data and Web technologies at the Department of Computer Science at Aalborg University. In this video he talks about communicating and documenting his research on his website, and how you can build up a website for sharing your research. He presents his website.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/history/</guid>
      <description>About Heading </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/resources/website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/resources/website/</guid>
      <description>Learn to build your own website. For individuals, research projects or groups, using only open source software and services.
Key facts Dates
 17.03.2021, 2 - 3.30pm 23.03.2021, 2 - 3.30pm 29.03.2021, 2 - 3.30pm  Time: 1.5h
Place: Zoom
  Lecturer Daniel is an Associate Professor in Data Science &amp;amp; Innovation Economics at the Aalborg University Business School, where he leads the Data Science research track at the AI:Growth lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter</title>
      <link>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/resources/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reachaaut.github.io/ReachAAUt-Site/resources/twitter/</guid>
      <description>By using social media, you will get a larger audience and can increase the reach of your research (recent studies show how tweeting about research papers significantly increase the number of citations.) With a single tweet, you can quickly and easily reach out to people from all over the world. Twitter is a great and simple platform to share your content without any special equipment other than your phone or computer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
